[
    {
        "id": "t1b4r2b0",
        "status": "upcoming",
        "winnerId": null,
        "team1": null,
        "team2": null
    },
    {
        "id": "t1b4r1b0",
        "status": "upcoming",
        "winnerId": null,
        "team1":
        {
            "id": 1,
            "name": "Team name 1",
            "owner": "0x385Eeac5cB85A38A9a07A70c73e0a3271CfB54A7",
            "leader": 1,
            "back1": 1,
            "back1Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "PolterGeist",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g1_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g1_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g1_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g1_right.svg",
                "brs": 569,
                "kinship": 829,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eys": 3,
                "eyc": 11,
                "specialId": 1,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": -228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 1
            },
            "back2": null,
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3": 2,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
                "brs": 540,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 3,
                "xp": 100,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eys": 100,
                "eyc": 101,
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "evade": 40,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 60,
                "armor": 70,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 80,
                "onchainId": 2
            },
            "back4": null,
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5": 4,
            "back5Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 4,
                "name": "Casper",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g4_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g4_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g4_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g4_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 6,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 4
            },
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 3,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 3,
                "name": "TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g3_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g3_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g3_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g3_right.svg",
                "brs": 0,
                "kinship": 0,
                "level": 0,
                "xp": 0,
                "nrg": 0,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 0,
                "brn": 0,
                "eys": 0,
                "eyc": 0,
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 0,
                "health": 0,
                "accuracy": 0,
                "evade": 0,
                "physical": 0,
                "magic": 0,
                "armor": 0,
                "crit": 0,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 3
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 5,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 5,
                "name": "Orko",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g5_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g5_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g5_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g5_right.svg",
                "brs": 520,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eys": 23,
                "eyc": 42,
                "specialId": 5,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": -228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 5
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        },
        "team2":
        {
            "id": 2,
            "name": "Team name 2 Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
            "owner": "0x86935F11C86623deC8a25696E1C19a8659CbF95d",
            "leader": 9,
            "back1": null,
            "back1Gotchi": null,
            "back2": 10,
            "back2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 10,
                "name": "Hopkirk",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 2,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 10
            },
            "back3": 9,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 9,
                "name": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 9
            },
            "back4": 7,
            "back4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 7,
                "name": "Moaning Myrtle",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g7_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g7_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g7_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g7_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 4,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 7
            },
            "back5": null,
            "back5Gotchi": null,
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 6,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 6,
                "name": "Nearly-Headless Nick",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 3,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 6
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 8,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 8,
                "name": "Peeves",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g8_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g8_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g8_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g8_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 8
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "t1b4r1b2",
        "status": "upcoming",
        "winnerId": null,
        "team1":
        {
            "id": 3,
            "name": "Team name 3 TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
            "owner": "0x86935F11C86623deC8a25696E1C19a8659CbF95d",
            "leader": 1,
            "back1": 1,
            "back1Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "PolterGeist",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g1_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g1_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g1_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g1_right.svg",
                "brs": 569,
                "kinship": 829,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eys": 3,
                "eyc": 11,
                "specialId": 1,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": -228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 1
            },
            "back2": null,
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3": 2,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
                "brs": 540,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 3,
                "xp": 100,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eys": 100,
                "eyc": 101,
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "evade": 40,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 60,
                "armor": 70,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 80,
                "onchainId": 2
            },
            "back4": null,
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5": 4,
            "back5Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 4,
                "name": "Casper",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g4_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g4_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g4_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g4_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 6,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 4
            },
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 3,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 3,
                "name": "TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g3_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g3_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g3_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g3_right.svg",
                "brs": 0,
                "kinship": 0,
                "level": 0,
                "xp": 0,
                "nrg": 0,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 0,
                "brn": 0,
                "eys": 0,
                "eyc": 0,
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 0,
                "health": 0,
                "accuracy": 0,
                "evade": 0,
                "physical": 0,
                "magic": 0,
                "armor": 0,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 3
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 5,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 5,
                "name": "Orko",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g5_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g5_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g5_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g5_right.svg",
                "brs": 520,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eys": 23,
                "eyc": 42,
                "specialId": 5,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": -228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 5
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        },
        "team2":
        {
            "id": 4,
            "name": "Team name 4 - Test my team",
            "owner": "0xBfe09443556773958bae1699b786d8E9680B5571",
            "leader": 9,
            "back1": null,
            "back1Gotchi": null,
            "back2": 10,
            "back2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 10,
                "name": "Hopkirk",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 2,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 10
            },
            "back3": 9,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 9,
                "name": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 9
            },
            "back4": 7,
            "back4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 7,
                "name": "Moaning Myrtle",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g7_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g7_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g7_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g7_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 4,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 7
            },
            "back5": null,
            "back5Gotchi": null,
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 6,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 6,
                "name": "Nearly-Headless Nick",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 3,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 6
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 8,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 8,
                "name": "Peeves",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g8_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g8_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g8_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g8_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 8
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "t1b2r1b0",
        "status": "completed",
        "winnerId": 1,
        "team1":
        {
            "id": 1,
            "name": "Team name 1",
            "owner": "0x385Eeac5cB85A38A9a07A70c73e0a3271CfB54A7",
            "leader": 1,
            "back1": 1,
            "back1Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "PolterGeist",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g1_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g1_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g1_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g1_right.svg",
                "brs": 569,
                "kinship": 829,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 21,
                "agg": 79,
                "spk": 88,
                "brn": 76,
                "eys": 3,
                "eyc": 11,
                "specialId": 1,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": -228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 1
            },
            "back2": null,
            "back2Gotchi": null,
            "back3": 2,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g2_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g2_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g2_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g2_right.svg",
                "brs": 540,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 3,
                "xp": 100,
                "nrg": -1,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 1,
                "brn": 99,
                "eys": 100,
                "eyc": 101,
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 10,
                "health": 20,
                "accuracy": 30,
                "evade": 40,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 60,
                "armor": 70,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 80,
                "onchainId": 2
            },
            "back4": null,
            "back4Gotchi": null,
            "back5": 4,
            "back5Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 4,
                "name": "Casper",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g4_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g4_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g4_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g4_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 6,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 4
            },
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 3,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 3,
                "name": "TestingLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWordLongWord",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g3_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g3_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g3_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g3_right.svg",
                "brs": 0,
                "kinship": 0,
                "level": 0,
                "xp": 0,
                "nrg": 0,
                "agg": 0,
                "spk": 0,
                "brn": 0,
                "eys": 0,
                "eyc": 0,
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 0,
                "health": 0,
                "accuracy": 0,
                "evade": 0,
                "physical": 0,
                "magic": 0,
                "armor": 0,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 3
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 5,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 5,
                "name": "Orko",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g5_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g5_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g5_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g5_right.svg",
                "brs": 520,
                "kinship": 1000,
                "level": 6,
                "xp": 820,
                "nrg": 4,
                "agg": 8,
                "spk": 15,
                "brn": 16,
                "eys": 23,
                "eyc": 42,
                "specialId": 5,
                "speed": 146,
                "health": -228,
                "accuracy": 71,
                "evade": 23,
                "physical": 150,
                "magic": 380,
                "armor": 1,
                "crit": 2,
                "resist": 0,
                "onchainId": 5
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        },
        "team2":
        {
            "id": 2,
            "name": "Team name 2 Testing Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String Long String",
            "owner": "0x86935F11C86623deC8a25696E1C19a8659CbF95d",
            "leader": 9,
            "back1": null,
            "back1Gotchi": null,
            "back2": 10,
            "back2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 10,
                "name": "Hopkirk",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 2,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 10
            },
            "back3": 9,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 9,
                "name": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 9
            },
            "back4": 7,
            "back4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 7,
                "name": "Moaning Myrtle",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g7_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g7_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g7_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g7_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 4,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 7
            },
            "back5": null,
            "back5Gotchi": null,
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 6,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 6,
                "name": "Nearly-Headless Nick",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 3,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 6
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 8,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 8,
                "name": "Peeves",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g8_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g8_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g8_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g8_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 8
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "t1b2r1b4",
        "status": "completed",
        "winnerId": 5,
        "team1":
        {
            "id": 5,
            "name": "Team name 5 - Test my team",
            "owner": "0xBfe09443556773958bae1699b786d8E9680B5571",
            "leader": 9,
            "back1": null,
            "back1Gotchi": null,
            "back2": 10,
            "back2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 10,
                "name": "Hopkirk",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g10_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g10_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g10_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g10_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 2,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 10
            },
            "back3": 9,
            "back3Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 9,
                "name": "Obi Wan Kenobi",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g9_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g9_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g9_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g9_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 7,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 9
            },
            "back4": 7,
            "back4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 7,
                "name": "Moaning Myrtle",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g7_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g7_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g7_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g7_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 4,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 7
            },
            "back5": null,
            "back5Gotchi": null,
            "front1": null,
            "front1Gotchi": null,
            "front2": 6,
            "front2Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 6,
                "name": "Nearly-Headless Nick",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g6_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g6_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g6_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g6_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 3,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 6
            },
            "front3": null,
            "front3Gotchi": null,
            "front4": 8,
            "front4Gotchi":
            {
                "id": 8,
                "name": "Peeves",
                "svgFront": "/dev/gotchi_g8_front.svg",
                "svgBack": "/dev/gotchi_g8_back.svg",
                "svgLeft": "/dev/gotchi_g8_left.svg",
                "svgRight": "/dev/gotchi_g8_right.svg",
                "brs": 500,
                "kinship": 5000,
                "level": 5,
                "xp": 5000,
                "nrg": 50,
                "agg": 50,
                "spk": 50,
                "brn": 50,
                "eys": 50,
                "eyc": 50,
                "specialId": 8,
                "speed": 50,
                "health": 50,
                "accuracy": 50,
                "evade": 50,
                "physical": 50,
                "magic": 50,
                "armor": 50,
                "crit": 50,
                "resist": 50,
                "onchainId": 8
            },
            "front5": null,
            "front5Gotchi": null
        },
        "team2": null
    }
]